Adam Darby

Web Developer

Motivated web developer with 15+ years of experience working in a myriad of environments, both development and team-wise. Passionate and hard-working with the ability to adapt to any given situation. Excellent communications skills and positive demeanor, works well with people from varying backgrounds and cultures.

Work History

2016-01 -Front End Web Developer 2019-11

FortyFour, Atlanta, GA I worked as part of the development team to design and implement solutions for clients of all stripes. Magento, Drupal, Shopify, Wordpress, HTML5, CSS/SCSS, Javascript/jQuery. Built and updated Magento pages for Coca-Cola USA (cokestore.com) and Coke France.

2014-12 -Front-End Web Developer

2015-12 Tin Roof Software, Atlanta, GA Worked with other developers to build an interface for

CNN Go for DirecTV's set-top box and the Amazon Fire Stick (Angular, HTML, CSS). Also helped build CNN's Great Big Story site (React).

2010-03 -**User Interface Developer** 2014-10

Engauge, Atlanta, GA Worked with the design, UX, and content teams to create client websites, emails, and Facebook applications using HTML, CSS, Javascript, and the Codelgniter framework.

2009-11 -Web Developer

2010-03 WebMD Health Corp., Atlanta, GA Worked with designers and other developers to create and update features on the WebMD site.

2009-03 -Web Developer 2009-06

Contact

Address

585 Willowbrook Run Alpharetta, Georgia, 30022

Phone

(404) 916-0919

E-mail

kyds3k@gmail.com

Skills

HTMI



CSS/SASS/LESS



Javascript



JQuery



Web development projects



Very Good

Agile workflow processes



Very Good

Website optimization



Maybe For You, Inc., Atlanta, GA

Created client sites and updated/upgraded existing client sites. Worked with another agency to develop and update WAI-ARIA compliance for the College Board.

2008-08 - Web Developer

2009-03 Cartoon Network, Atlanta, GA

Worked with designers and backed team to create the landing and launch website for Cartoon Network's *FusionFall MMO*.

2006-09 - Web Developer

Superdeluxe/Turner Broadcasting, Atlanta, GA
Worked with development and design teams to launch
the Superdeluxe site (note: not connected to the
current Superdeluxe website besides being a Turner
product). Built a Yahoo desktop app to provide users
with the latest videos and artist page updates.

Education

2008-05

1992-08 - Bachelor of Science: Technical Writing

1996-12 Carnegie Mellon University - Pittsburgh